const javaScriptData = [
    {
        "question": "Which keyword is used to declare a global variable in JavaScript?",
        "options": ["var","let","const","variable"],
        "answer": "var"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of typeof [] in JavaScript?",
        "options": ["array","object","array-like","list"],
        "answer": "object"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which built-in method adds one or more elements to the end of an array and returns the new length of the array?",
        "options": ["push()","append()","addToEnd()","insert()"],
        "answer": "push()"
    },
    {
        "question": "What will console.log(2 + '2') print in JavaScript?",
        "options": ["22","4","2 + '2'","TypeError"],
        "answer": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the JavaScript operator for checking equality without type coercion?",
        "options": ["==","===","=","eq"],
        "answer": "==="
    },
    {
        "question": "Which function is used to parse a string and return it as a floating point number in JavaScript?",
        "options": ["parseInt()","parseFloat()","toNumber()","convertToFloat()"],
        "answer": "parseFloat()"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the && operator do in JavaScript?",
        "options": ["Logical OR","Logical NOT","Logical AND","Bitwise AND"],
        "answer": "Logical AND"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which keyword is used to exit from a loop in JavaScript?",
        "options": ["stop","exit","break","end"],
        "answer": "break"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the typeof operator return for null in JavaScript?",
        "options": ["null","undefined","object","NaN"],
        "answer": "object"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which method is used to remove the last element from an array in JavaScript?",
        "options": ["pop()","removeLast()","deleteLast()","splice()"],
        "answer": "pop()"
    }    

]

export { javaScriptData}